LEIGH B. BIENEN PAPERS (APAP312) 1872, 1935, 1951-2011, Undated
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Faculty Papers and Scholarly Research Material, 1979-2011, Undated; 2; 7
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [3 of 4], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment [4 of 4], 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan articles on Illinois Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, Comments on the Illinois State's Attorney's Association Response to the Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Repair or Repeal - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment", 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Illinois State Budget and Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Charles Johnson, "A Bootcamp for Creative Writing ", 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Letter from Governor Rod R. Blagojevich, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Office if the State's Attorneys Appellate Prosecutor - Report on the Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Persuasion Assignment - naked documents, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Seminar Task Force Report: murder and it's consequences, Fall 2002 - "The Status of the Death Penalty in Illinois as of January 13, 2003", Northwestern University School of Law (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - John Cullerton, Kirk Dillard, and Peter G. Baroni, "Capital Punishment in Illinois - A model for the Nation" - Internet Printout, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - John Cullerton, Kirk Dillard, and Peter G. Baroni, "Capital Punishment Reform in Illinois: A model for the Nation", 2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Illinois House Bill 0576 - Police Training Act, ca. 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Molly Treadway Johnson and Laural L. Hopper, Resource Guide for Managing Capital Cases: Volume I, Federal Death Penalty Trials, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lafonso Rollins - footnote for procedures to get wrongful conviction claim, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Capital punishment Reform - What's Been Done and what Remains to be Done", 2004 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Preventing Wrongful Convictions: A Current Report from Illinois", 2004 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", with annotations, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", 2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rob Warden, "Illinois Death Penalty Reform: How it Happened, what it Promises", 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - "Death Penalty Decision Guidelines", prepared by the office of the Illinois Attorney General and the Illinois State's Attorney Association, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mary E. Forsberg, "Money for Nothing? The Financial Cost of New Jersey's Death Penalty", 2006 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Historical Northwestern University Legal Aid, Legal Clinics, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Historical Research on late 19th and early 20th century crimes, 2006; 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Illinois Capital Punishment information - Christopher Tansey Capital Litigation Trust Fund data, Annotation of Capital Punishment Reform Provision, First Degree murder Summary table, State Death Penalty Decision Guidelines, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Lethal Injection - Saddamn Hussein, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Lethal Injection - Henry Weinstein, Los Angeles Times Staff writer, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Glenn L. Pierce and Michael L. Radelet, "The Impact of Legally Inappropriate Factors on Death Sentencing for California Homicides", 2006 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Slides Draft - Illinois Violent Death Reporting System, ca. 2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Summary of Indictments for Murder on Illinois in which a notice of intent to seek capital punishment was filed, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Washington State Bar Association: Final Report of the Death Penalty Subcommittee of the committee on Public Defense, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cook County Appropriations data, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - FBI crime report on Homicides, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Illinois Crime Index Offense/Crime Index Offense Arrest Data, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Illinois Criminal Code - Appellate procedures, reversals, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Illinois Judicial Circuits, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Illinois Law Enforcement training- recording of homicide interrogations, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Illinois Mandate to create Capital Crimes Database, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Illinois Violent Death Reporting System, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Legislative Statutes - New Jersey and New Mexico, 2007; 2009 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Lethal Injection - Animal Liberation Front, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Lethal Injection - AVMA Guidelines on Euthanasia, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Lethal Injection - Deborah W. Denno, "The Lethal Injection Quandary: How Medicine Has Dismantled the Death Penalty, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Lethal Injection - Euthanasia Statutes, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Lethal Injection - Dead Animal disposal, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Lethal Injection - Oregon Death with Dignity Act, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Lethal Injection - Mad Cow, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Lethal Injection - Toledo Blade, Michael Manning botched lethal injection suit, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - New Jersey bills repealing the death penalty, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - New Jersey Capital Punishment Report - typed notes, ca. 2007 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Thomas P. Sullivan, "Efforts to Improve the Illinois Capital Punishment System: worth the Cost?" (with annotations), 2007 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Table 1 - Results of published studies reporting the costs associated with processing capital cases (from "The Cost of the Death Penalty in Maryland"), ca. 2007 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Wrongful Conviction Awards - Illinois, Washington, California, Nebraska, Utah, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Leigh B. Bienen, "Not wiser after 35 years of Contemplating the Death Penalty", 2008 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Joseph E. Birkett op-ed on death penalty reforms in 2002, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Bureau of Justice Statistics Capital Punishment data for 2008 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund and general costs of death penalty, 2008; 2009 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - "Death Penalty Reform in Illinois: Five Years of Failure" - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual Report, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Jon B. Gould and Lisa Greenman, "Update on the Cost, Quality, and Availability of Defense Representation in Federal Death Penalty Case: Preliminary Report on Phase One of the Research", 2008 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Jon B. Gould and Lisa Greenman, "Update on the Cost, Quality, and Availability of Defense Representation in Federal Death Penalty Case: Preliminary Report on Phase One of the Research", 2008; 2010 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Barbara J. Hayler, "Moratorium and Reform: Illinois's Efforts to Make the Death Penalty Process 'Fair, Just, and Accurate'", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jessica S. Henry, "New Jersey's Road to Abolition", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Court System - expenditures table, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Report, Post - Clemency Era, ca. 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Crime rate and prison population data, 2008; 2009 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Illinois Treasurer proposes reform in litigation Fund", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lethal Injection - Jim Speta question about administration of federal Animal Protection Act, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - John Roman et. al., "The Cost of the Death Penalty in Maryland", 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Elliot Slosar, "Costs of Capital Punishment in Illinois", ca. 2008 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Summaries of Illinois Death Row Convictions Since 2003, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Summaries of Illinois Death Row Convictions Since 2003, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Syllabus - Writing for a Professional Audience and Beyond, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Table of Illinois Executions, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Texas capital punishment racial disparities study, 2008; 2009 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Jeffrey Toobin, "Death in Georgia" (cite in FN), 2008 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 771 indictments for First Degree Murder in Illinois 2003-2009 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - A base of Governor Pardoning Power, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Al Baker, "Homicides Near Record Low Rate In New York City" (FN 141), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Katherine Barnes, et. al., "Place Matters (Most): An Empirical Study of Prosecutorial Decision - Making in Death - Eligible Cases" (cited around FN 136), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Appointed Counsel Expenses from Fiscal Years 2000-2009, ca. 2009 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund with notes, 2009; 2010 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Chicago Murder Conviction Cases, 2004; 2009 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Citation - David Baldus Nebraska Study, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Citation - Nationally death sentences down and reaction to Ohio op-ed arguing that lethal injection is inhumane, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Colorado State Budget, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Cook County Employees Salaries, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Cook County, Illinois Budget - State's Attorney, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cook County Illinois Obligations, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Cook County Public Defender Salaries, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Philip J. Cook, "Potential Savings from Abolition of the Death Penalty in North Carolina" (with annotations), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2009; 2010 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - Dilliard Cost and Jurisdiction of New Jersey Appellate Courts, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Crime in Illinois 1971 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Crime in Illinois 1985 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Crime in Illinois 2000 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Crime in Illinois 1990 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Crime in Illinois 1998 - Historical Statistics, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Crime in Illinois 2005 - Historical Statistics (used in "Capital Punishment in Illinois in the Aftermath of the Ryan Commutations"), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Brian Dugan Article (FN 194/196), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Brian Dugan defense costs, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Amanda Enyeart - table of Illinois Supreme Court Death Penalty Opinions, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Fiscal Impact of Abolition of death penalty in New Mexico, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Fiscal Impact of Abolition in New Jersey and New Mexico, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Georgia Proportionality Review - Stevens Statement (quote), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Historical Evolution of Illinois Death Penalty Legislation, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Illinois Capital Cases, Cook County, 2009; 2010; Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act Amendments, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Research Material, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Illinois Capital Litigation Fund Data - Jonathan Sabo, 2009; 2010 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual Report, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Illinois crime data from 2003 - 2009 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Illinois Criminal Procedure and Capital Crimes Litigation Acts from 1999 to 2009 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Reversals Law, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Illinois Health Care Worker Background Check Act, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Illinois House Bill 0262 (Death Penalty Abolition), 2009 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Illinois House Bill 262 - Death Penalty Abolition, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Illinois Office of the State Appellate Defender - Annual Report Fiscal Year 2009 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Illinois v. Salvador Ortiz - Actual Innocence Case, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Procedures in Capital Cases (cite), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Public Defender Compensation - Quote for Public Defender Salaries, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Illinois v. Rolando Cruz (1994), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Illinois State's Attorneys Salaries, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2001, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2002, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2003, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2004, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2005, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2006, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2007, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Illinois Traditional Budgetary Financial Report Fiscal Year 2008, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Illinois Wrongful Conviction Settlement Data, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Indiana Public Defender Cuts, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - January 1, 2004 report of the Cook County State's Attorney General's Office regarding monies received under Capital Crime Litigation Trust Fund Act, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Journal of Criminal Law & Criminology notes - typed notes from "Capital Punishment in Illinois in the Aftermath of the Ryan Commutations: Reforms, Economic Realities, and a new Saliency for Issues of Cost", 2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jeffrey L. Kirchmeier, et. al., "Vigilante Justice: Prosecutor Misconduct in Capital Cases" (with annotations), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Legislation used in footnotes, Washington House Bill 2864, California Legislation 432, Nebraska Legislation 260, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Marcia Lehr - indigent defense, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - New Jersey Amendments to Death Penalty Regulations (cite), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - New Jersey v. Robert O. Marshall (1992) - cite Handler's dissent, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Supreme Court Justice Daniel O'Hern, "What Makes a Court Supreme", 2009 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "New State Budget Crimps Justice Agencies", 2009 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina Innocence Inquiry Commission, 2009; 2010 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Northwestern Law Newsletter, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Notes - Illinois death sentences, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Kristen Nugent, "Proportionality and Prosecutorial Discretion…" good notes on Co. by Co. and on prosecutorial discretion, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Office of the State Appellate Defender Annual Report, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Research Notes on newspaper accounts of murders in Illinois, ca. 2009 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - John Schwartz, "Death Sentence Dropped But Executions Rose in '09" (FN 139), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "Smart on Crime: Reconsidering the Death Penalty in a Time of Economic Crisis" (cite), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Alex Song - Illinois v. Brian Nelson, Illinois v. Hanson, and Illinois v. Banks, 2009; 2010 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - State's Attorneys power and dates, discretion, and compensation, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - State's Attorney Salaries (quote), 2009 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Texas Governor James Ferguson and payments for pardons, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1986 Article on Robert Marshall's First Death Sentence, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 2009 Amendment to Illinois Capital Crimes Litigation Act, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - A Brief History of the Lethal Injection Debate since 2008 Compiled by Mark Christopher Frantz, ca. 2010 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Abolition and State Proposition, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Adams County First Degree Murders request, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Amendment to Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - American Law Institute on Capital Punishment, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Attorney General Determination and Federal Death Penalty, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Attorney General and Federal Death Penalty Approval, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Blind Lineups, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Bureau of Justice Statistics Crime and Justice Data Online, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Jon Burge Article (FN 193), 2010 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Capital Crimes Litigation Act - high lighted portions and changes, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Capital Litigation Fund Illinois Report, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - 2009 revisions, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund for Cook County - FOIA Request, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Correspondence, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund, fiscal years 2008 - 2010 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund - Printout with notes, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund Statistical Report, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Capital Litigation Trust Fund Statistics, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Capital Punishment Reform Study Committee Act of 2003, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Cases that assert no proportionality review for Illinois, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Citation - Illinois Supreme Court Case overturn death penalty, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Connecticut Death Penalty Articles, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Cook County Indictments 2003 - 2010 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Cook County - Capital Litigation Trust Funds, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence - Eligibility of non - statutory aggravating factors, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence - wrongful convictions awards (FN), 2010 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - John Council, "5th Circuit Judge Notes 'Kafkaesque' Result in Capital Case" (is quoted), 2010 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Crime in Illinois 2003, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Polls, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Death Penalty Research Titles, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Death Sentences overturned on basis on fundamental justice amendment, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Death Penalty Stance of 2002 Attorney General Candidates, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Ethics and Post conviction Waivers, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Federal and Attorney General guidelines for selection of capital cases, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Federal Lethal Injection Challenges, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Federal and State Concurrent Jurisdiction, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Doug Finke, "Committee Oks call to abolish death penalty in Illinois, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Samuel R. Gross, "Still Unfair, Still Arbitrary - But do we Care?" Keynote Address, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Illinois Attorney Statute, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Illinois Litigation Trust Fund legislation, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Illinois Clemency Power, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Illinois Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Annual meeting invitation, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Illinois Compiled Statute section on the Illinois Capital Litigation Trust Fund, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Decision Guidelines and Qualifications, 2010; Undated (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Illinois Courts Chat, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Illinois Court of Claims - wrongful convictions, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Sentencing instructions 2008 update, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Illinois Death Penalty Sentencing instructions current to 2008, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Illinois House Bill 5687, abolition of the death penalty, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Illinois Legislation - Decertification of full-time and part-time police officers, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Legislative History of Death Penalty Reform with annotations, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Pattern Instructions, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Illinois Pattern Jury Instructions - Death Penalty Cases 2008 Update (cite), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Illinois Seminars on Capital Cases, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Illinois Senate Bill 574 (1999), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Senate Bill 3569 - Death Penalty Abolition, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Illinois State Budget - Department of Corrections, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Illinois State Comptroller Contact Us, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Illinois Supreme Court Justices and former positions as prosecutors and state's Attorneys, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Illinois Supreme Court Rules, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Illinois Supreme Court Rules - Seminars on Capital Cases, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Illinois Tax Foundation, "A guide to the Illinois Appropriations Process", 2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Illinois v. Thompson (minutes), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Jackson County Board cuts public defender salary by $46,000" (cited), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Lake County and Kane County data, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Legal foundation for Illinois Governor's clemency power, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Marcia Lehr - wrongful conviction, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Letter to Michael J.Z. Mannheimer from Roger L. Thomas concerning Pennsylvania House bill 1996, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - List of Supreme Court cases that discuss not conducting Proportionality Review, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Material from Cecil E. Torres on Admissibility of mitigating evidence during a penalty phase trial, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Missouri Proportionality Review - Missouri v. Carman L. Deck, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "No Bail for Two Men Accused in Darien Murders", 2010 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Nonstatutory Aggravating Factors, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - NPR Coverage of Death Penalty costs in Illinois, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Notes - Illinois State's Attorneys salary cuts, ca. 2010 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Notes on ineffective Assistance of Counsel, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Pew Report of Pension Obligations, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Sarah Pfander - Illinois Murders by County, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Prosecutors Statements, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Public Defender Representation - Weis v. Georgia, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Research credit, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Responsible Budget Coalition (FN 64), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Reversals since 2003 reforms: Nelson, Lovejoy, Morris, Urdiales, Thompson, Mertz, and Albanese cases, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Small Illinois Counties and State's Attorneys and public defenders, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Sources on Blind lineups for footnote, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - State Statutes - California, Washington, Utah, Illinois, Nebraska, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Supreme Court and "any evidence" at penalty phase, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Supreme Court of New Jersey 2000, Proportionality Review Project, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Bidish Sarma, et. al., "Struck by Lightning: Walker v. Georgia and Louisiana's Proportionality Review of Death Sentences" (cite), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Christopher Michael Tansey, Appendix - Empirical Studies, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Christopher Tansey - Capital Litigation Trust Fund Expenditures, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Christopher Michael Tansey - Informal Bibliography, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Christopher Tansey Summary tables, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Michael P. Toomin, "Capital Punishment Reform and the Illinois Supreme Court: At the Forefront of change." (2004), 2010 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Three Articles on Brian Dugan and DuPage County death penalty, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Typed notes on Burge and Brian Dugan costs, ca. 2010 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - U.S. Census Homicide Trends 1980 to 2005, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 48)